Fourth, we're designing smart therapeutics that can do calculations within the body and go far beyond current medicines, which are really blunt instruments. For example, to target a small subset of immune cells responsible for an autoimmune disorder, and distinguish them from the vast majority of healthy immune cells. Finally, inspired by remarkable biological materials such as silk, abalone shell, tooth and others, we're designing new protein-based materials to address challenges in energy and ecological issues. To do all this, we're growing our institute. We seek to attract energetic, talented and diverse scientists from around the world, at all career stages, to join us. You can also participate in the protein design revolution through our online folding and design game, "Foldit." And through our distributed computing project, Rosetta@home, which you can join from your laptop or your Android smartphone. Making the world a better place through protein design is my life's work. I'm so excited about what we can do together. I hope you'll join us, and thank you. (Applause and cheers)
El cuarto, estamos diseñando terapéuticos inteligentes que hagan estimaciones y rebasen medicinas actuales, los cuales son instrumentos imprecisos. Por ejemplo, para dirigirse a un subconjunto de células inmunes responsables de un desorden autoinmune, y distinguirlas de la vasta mayoría de células inmunes saludables. Por último, inspirados en materiales biológicos sin igual, como seda, concha de abulón, dientes y otros, estamos diseñando nuevos materiales de proteínas para afrontar los desafíos en energías y ecología. Para lograr todo esto, nuestro instituto está creciendo. Deseamos atraer diversos científicos talentosos y llenos de energía de todo el mundo, en cualquier etapa de su carrera, para que se nos unan. También pueden participar en la revolución del diseño de proteínas a través de nuestro juego en línea de plegamiento y diseño "Foldit". Y a través de nuestro proyecto difundido de computadora "Rosetta@home", al cual pueden acceder desde su laptop y celular inteligente Android. Mi trabajo es hacer del mundo un lugar mejor a través del diseño de proteínas. Estoy tan entusiasmado de lo que podemos lograr juntos. Espero que se nos unan, y gracias. (Aplausos y ovaciones)